George Brata

Frontend Web Developer





Summary

Versatile frontend web developer with broad experience using all kinds of JS frameworks, but my favorite stack (currently) is Vue.js and Nuxt.js. I am passionate about education, the Internet, and blockchain technology - and everything that connects the three.

Experience

Vue.js Freelancer, BinarCode Mar 2022 - Present Designed, implemented, tested and documented frontend functionalities of a web-based job

Senior Vue.js Developer, SHE Information Technology

lan 2021 - Mar 2022

My responsibilities were maintaining a web platform based on FirstSpirit CMS, creating new Vue.js components with Bootstrap and providing support for multilingual content teams.

management platform using Vue.js, Tailwind, Pinia, FormKit, ElementIO and Netlify.

Jul 2018 - Dec 2020

Frontend Web Developer, **QCatalyst**

Building, testing, deploying and maintaining responsive consumer-facing web applications for National Geographic using modern technologies like React, Redux, Tailwind, Webpack, Storybook, Cypress and Docker.

Ul Developer, 3Pillar Global

Apr 2017 - Jul 2018

Developed financial education learning modules for a US-based client in a React.js app. As a team, we worked with tools like Github, CircleCl, JIRA, Browserstack and Confluence to deliver high-quality readable code and documentation.

lan 2016 - Apr 2017

Junior Web Developer, Yonder

Migrated a legacy app from Microsoft Silverlight to AngularJS and built the frontend of a completely new web app from scratch using Angular.js and Bulma CSS.

Feb 2016 - present

Trainer, Digital Kids Cluj-Napoca

In my spare time I teach children the computer skills they need to thrive in the 21st century, including the basics of programming, photo/video editing, robotics, web development and other digital abilities.

Education

2014 - 2015 2010 - 2014 Computer Science, Babes-Bolyai University, Cluj-Napoca Mathematics - Informatics, Emanuil Gojdu High School, Oradea

Why hire me?

Results-driven and people-oriented, I am feeling most comfortable in agile, fast-paced development environments. My passion is crafting modern web applications with great UX. Beside my regular frontend developer job, over the last 6 years I have built several freelancing <u>side-projects</u> and I went to a <u>dozen hackathons</u> to train those muscles.